<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    // Data for AttractionActivity.java
    <string name="victoria_memorial">Another relic of the British Raj in India, the Victoria Memorial is located in the heart of Kolkata, in West Bengal. This white marbled opulent structure was built in memory of Queen Victoria to celebrate her 25 years of rule over India and is almost a replica of the Victoria Memorial in London. Victoria Memorial is an iconic structure that is synonymous with the city of joy!\n\nThe memorial is surrounded by a lush green and well-maintained garden, which spreads over 64 acres and has numerous statues and sculptures in it. A sixteen-foot tall bronze statue of victory, mounted on ball bearings at the top of the memorial, serves to heighten the overall appeal and grandeur of the entire complex. Victoria Memorial is breathtaking and marvellous, especially at night, when it is illuminated. The Sound and Light shows that take place in the evening are an added delight, and a must watch. All in all, the place is a must visit for people to wish to relive the essence of the Victorian era in the modern day world.</string>
    <string name="william_fort">The mighty edifice of Fort William is situated in the city of Kolkata, on the eastern bank of the  Hooghly River. Built in the year 1696, the fort is named after King William III and was the first stronghold of the British in the country. The magnificent structure is spread over 70.9 acres and is embellished with hundreds of arched windows that overlook lush green gardens. Meticulous stonework adorns the surface of the building and it took as long as took ten years to reach completion. However, it was soon realized that the building had a few loopholes, and a new octagonal building was constructed whose foundation was laid by Sir Robert Clive.\n\nOver the course of its existence, Fort William has served a number of purposes, each of which was in stark contrast to the other. Initially, it comprised of wings and an inner bastion where prisoners were hauled which is why it was known as \'the black hole of Calcutta\'. Today, Fort William is the property of the Indian Army and has a capacity of accommodating up to 10,000 army personnel. It also serves as the headquarters of the Eastern Command. Due to its importance with respect to Indian intelligence, access to the interiors of the fort is limited to army personnel and their relatives. However, you can visit the palace for its stunning architecture.</string>
    <string name="belur_math">Belur Math in Kolkata is the headquarters of the Ramakrishna Math and Mission. Sprawling over forty acres of land on the west bank of the Hooghly River, it is visited by people from all over the world, irrespective of their religious beliefs.\n\nThe temple is known for its distinctive architecture, which fuses Hindu, Christian and Islamic motifs as a symbol of unity of all religions. Founded by Swami Vivekananda, the chief disciple of Ramakrishna Paramahansa, the temple is at the heart of the Ramakrishna Movement. The temple complex also houses a museum and several other affiliated educational institutions. The evening Aarti takes place 5:30 PM, at which an evening bell is rung to indicate that visitors are not allowed to loiter on the Math grounds and are also not allowed to visit any temple other than Sri Ramakrishna temple. The Aarti songs sung are hymns of praise to Sri Ramakrishna and Sri Sarada Devi. The Aarti here is different from those at other places of worship since one is expected just to sit and meditate. There is no religious offering made. Flowers and sweets are not offered.</string>
    <string name="howrah_bridge">An iconic landmark of Kolkata, Howrah Bridge is a massive steel bridge constructed over the Hooghly River. It is considered to be among the longest cantilever bridges in the world. Also known as Rabindra Setu, it connects Howrah and Kolkata. It carries daily traffic of over 100,000 vehicles and countless pedestrians and is as historic as it is grand. The opulence of the bridge, however, comes alive in the night time as it is all lit up. You can also take a ferry ride as it runs between Kolkata and Howrah, from the launch ghat. The view of the city from the ferry, especially in the night, is priceless, to say the least.\n\nHowrah Bridge was the third-longest cantilever bridge at the time of its construction, but now it is the sixth-longest one of its types. It was renamed as Rabindra Setu on June 14, 1965, after the name of Nobel Laureate Rabindranath Tagore. It spreads about 1500 ft over the Hooghly River and is 71 ft wide. There is a total of 8 lanes of strand road, bicycles, and pedestrians. What makes this bridge unique is the fact that it was built without a single nut or bolt and is held together by rivets.</string>
    <string name="birla_planetarium">Situated at the famous Chowringhee Road right in the proximity of Victoria Memorial and St. Paul\'s Cathedral Birla planetarium is the largest planetarium in Asia and the second largest in the world! Situated in the city of joy - Kolkata, Birla Planetarium is a magnificent edifice set up by Pandit Jawaharlal Nehru on 2nd July 1963. It is one of the three planetariums present in India. Also known as Taramandal, the Birla Planetarium regularly holds many shows and programs are in various languages including Hindi, English, Bengali, and other regional languages. In addition to being a planetarium, Birla Planetarium also has an electronics laboratory and an astronomy gallery that has a collection of paintings and astronomical models.\n\nA visit to the Birla Planetarium is an exciting way to ignite your interest in science and the motion of planets. People, especially astronomy lovers, arrive from all over the world to experience the amazing shows organized here. A trip here includes a tour of the planets, where interesting details about them and the other fascinating celestial bodies present in our universe are discussed. Silence rings loud while the show goes on, which in itself is a testament to the mesmerising effect of the shows here. Pictures of famous astronauts and other celestial bodies are put on display in the hallway. One can have a look at them after attending the show.</string>
    <string name="indian_museum">The ninth oldest museum of the world and largest in India, the Indian Museum is located in the city of joy - Kolkata. The foundation stone of the Indian Museum was laid down in the year 1814 and has been a centre of multidisciplinary activities ever since. Popularly known as \'Jadughar\', it has the finest collection of contemporary paintings, sacred relics of Buddha, Egyptian mummies and ancient sculptures. In addition to these, the Indian Museum boasts of some of the most exquisite collections of ornaments, fossils, skeletons, antiques, armours, and stunning Mughal paintings.\n\nPresently, the museum has 35 galleries which have been divided into six categories namely Art, Archaeology, Anthropology, Geology, Zoology and Economic Botany. For those inquisitive about history, there is also a library and bookshop present within the museum premises. Indian Museum recently celebrated its bicentennial anniversary with great fervour in February 2014. With its splendid collection, the museum takes you back in time to witness our fascinating past.</string>
    <string name="marble_palace_mansion">The Marble palace near the Chorbagan in North Kolkata built in 1835 by Rajendra Mallick is famed for its art collection of masterpieces by Reuben and paintings by various renowned international artists such as Reynolds, Van Gogh and Rembrandt.\n\nThe Palace also boasts of a Zoo with different rare birds and animals.</string>
    <string name="mother_house">Mother House or Missionaries of Charity is a religious congregation that was established by Mother Teresa in 1950. It is a Latin Church or a Roman Catholic religious congregation known as Saint Teresa of Kolkata. The members of the Mother House provide free services to the ones stricken by poverty. The house has about 4,500 members of the congregation, commonly known as Sisters who have selflessly devoted their lives to serve the poor and the needy ones. They adhere to the vows of obedience, poverty, chastity and to selflessly and wholeheartedly help to the ones who have been affected by poverty. Their service and kindness have won many a hearts, and today several branches are running all over the world serving the ones who are in need.\n\nThe missionaries provide free services to people in need regardless of their religion. They help the sick, the poor, the disabled, the mentally challenged, the ones who are dying, former prostitutes, the addicts, the homeless, the victims of natural disasters and epidemics, orphans and street children. They also run soup kitchens and schools to educate poor street children.\n\nAn area of the house is reserved for followers to pay their respect to Mother Teresa. Here, one can find Mother Teresa\'s Tomb and an exhibition that displays her work through photographs, awards and articles. Some of her belongings like her sarees, her sandals and her bag are also displayed. This is where Mother Teresa began her service to mankind, and this is where it ended. In her lifetime, she created a community that continues to serve the needy ones selflessly. One visit here to pay respects to Mother Teresa is a must.</string>
    <string name="science_city">One of its kind in India, the Science city was inaugurated on 1st July 1997. It is a major attraction for the residents of Kolkata as well as for the people visiting Kolkata. It is one of the finest and the largest science museums in the world and provides a fun way of learning science. Under the National Council of Science Museums, the Science City in Kolkata is the largest science centre in the entire Indian Subcontinent. It is a governmental organisation under the Ministry of Culture and the main motto of the Science City was the popularisation of science. It is located at the crossing of the EM Bypass and the JBS Halder Avenue in Kolkata. The science city is a perfect blend of education with fun. There is a special section dedicated to the aquatic world wherein you can learn every minute detail about the various fishes and insects in the aquatic world. Some of the most exotic fishes can be seen in these aquariums. All in all, science city is going to offer you a phenomenal experience with your friends and family and totally make your holiday worth it.\n\nThe ground floor of the science city comprises of some optical illusions which are very interesting to look at. It is always so much fun to watch yourself taking a variety of shapes in front of the optical mirrors. The city is located on the crossing of Eastern Bypass and Park Circus at Kolkata and should be a sure shot stop on your trip to Kolkata. It is a favourite amongst kids as well as adults. Tornado, the energy ball, ocean waves and quicksand are a must watch. Time Machine is a common favourite amongst all the visitors. It gives one the opportunity to travel to outer space from where you can travel back in time and enter the age of dinosaurs by being a part of the artificial Jurassic Park. You can try the ropeway as well and get a bird\'s eye view of the city.</string>
    <string name="st_paul_cathedral">Located in the heart of the City of Joy - Kolkata, St Paul\'s is an Anglican cathedral that operates under CNI – Church of North India. It is a must-visit for those who seek enriching historical and architectural pleasure on their vacation trips. In the heart of the city, this colossal structure reminds you of the colonial times and takes you down the memory lane. Travellers keep this among the top few must-visit places when they come to Kolkata. It looks most beautiful during the Christmas holidays, when the cathedral, the garden around it as well as the surrounding streets are all bathed in light and festivities.\n\nPrimarily built to accommodate the ever-increasing Christian community in Calcutta, it is the first Episcopalian church in Asia. The building follows Indo-Gothic style and its structure is complete with a cascading white edifice, towering spire and colourful tinted windows. Inside, it has a huge nave, majestic altar and chancel, along with carvings and paintings depicting great moments and events of Christian history. The cathedral complex also houses several memorabilia of past congregants and a library where books as old as the church\'s foundation time still exist donated by founding member Bishop Wilson.</string>
    <string name="tajpur">Tucked between Mandarmani and Shankarpur, Tajpur is a small town set on the Bay of Bengal\'s tranquil shore, just 170 kms from Kolkata. Considered to be a serene secret of West Bengal, the virgin beach is hidden away from view and is still untouched by commercialization and tourism. The highlight of the pristine beach are the hundreds of red crabs that are found on the shores, which also give a perfect crimson colour to the beach.\n\nBereft of chaos and cacophony, it provides the perfect escape from the hustle-bustle of city life. Besides, unlike the usual crescent-shaped beaches, this one is an inverted crimson in shape. Fringed by dense eucalyptus, tamarisk and casuarina trees, the secluded beach is perfect for lazing on a hammock and spending some time in solitude amidst the sun, sea and sand.</string>
    <string name="birla_madir">Birla Mandir is a stunning structure that adorns the streets of Ballygunge, Kolkata dedicated to Lord Krishna and Goddess Radha. An imposing structure amalgamating traditional style of architecture with modern reflections, the temple is the perfect specimen of craftsmanship and engineering genius. The construction of this splendid edifice began in the year 1970 and after meticulous work spanning over 26 years, it reached its completion on 21st February 1996. The unique patterns on the wall of the temple are sculpted by the artisans specially called from Agra, Mirzapur and Muzaffarpur. Although the chief deities of the temple is Krishna and Radha, other Gods revered here are Lord Ganesha, Lord Hanuman, Lord Shiva, ten avatars of Lord Vishnu and Goddess Durga.\n\nThe magnificent structure of the Birla Temple is hard to miss once you reach its vicinity. Towering domes covered in intricate stonework and design adorn the main facade of the temple, while the complex itself is a pearl white marble marvel. In addition to these, some artefacts in the temple are made up of silver and Belgian glass which impart a unique divinity to the shrine. As the dusk approaches, the beautiful Birla Mandir sight to behold adorned with electric diyas and gleaming chandeliers. The continuous chanting and soft music only add to its spiritual charm. With spectacular architecture, devotees and visitors come here from all around the globe, especially during Janmashtami which is celebrated here with great vigour.</string>
    <string name="eden_garden">Home of cricket in Kolkata, The Eden Gardens is a beautiful, well-maintained cricket stadium located in Kolkata\'s B. B. D. Bagh area, near State Secretariat and Calcutta High Court. It was established in the year 1864 and was laid by Governor- General Auckland, who named the gardens and the cricket ground after his sisters Emily and Fanny Eden. Stretched over 50 acres, this cricket stadium has the capacity to seat about 66,349 people and is the second largest stadiums in the world. When it is not hosting some of the most nail-biting sporting events, Eden Gardens also doubles up as a quaint destination for nature lovers.\n\nThe verdant pathways of Eden Gardens are shaded by huge mahogany, mango and banyan trees that make it a peaceful place to sit and enjoy the marvels of nature. There is also a three-storeyed Burmese Pagoda in red and golden yellow that was brought here by Lord Dalhousie. Eden Gardens Stadium plays host to many sports, most importantly cricket, which takes place lies right across the garden. Extremely popular as a sporting destination, it regularly hosts one day, test and T20 matches. Presently it is the home turf of IPL Team Kolkata Knight Riders and the regional Bengal Cricket Team. Eden Garden is also known to host several Association Matches. You can visit the stadium when no matches are being held. In order to do so, you need permission from CAB or Cricket Association of Bengal.</string>
    <string name="jorasanko_thakur_bari">The Bengali name for the House of the Thakurs, the Jorasanko Thakur Bari is the ancestral home of the Tagore family that is located in Jorasanko, in the north of Kolkata in West Bengal in India. This is an enjoyable and exciting place to visit, especially for lovers of history and Bengali literature. The 700 paintings that are exhibited in this ancestral home especially capture the attention of the visitors. What enthrals them, even more, is the self-composed invite of Rabindranath Tagore\'s wedding. The museum also houses three different galleries, manuscripts, books and other antique items.\n\nAll know the contributions of Rabindranath Tagore to the world of literature, and it is in this house that this exceptional poet was born and where he spent most of his life and then left for his heavenly abode. This ancestral home was built in the year 1784, and now houses the Rabindra Bharati Museum, which is commonly known as Jorasankho Thakurbari in the local language. The Rabindra Bharti University is also located in proximity to the Jorasanko Thakur Bari, and the university was started with the purpose of imparting quality education to the students.\n\nDetailed knowledge about the first Non-European Nobel Laureate, Rabindranath Tagore, can be obtained when one decides to visit the Jorasanko Thakur Bari. And then, of course, the chance to explore the history and lifestyle of such an eminent personality who has greatly shaped the literature that we know today is indeed unparalleled. This is precisely why the Jorasanko Thakur Bari should be on the top of your list of places to visit while in Kolkata!</string>
    <string name="birla_industrial_technological">Being the first scientific and industrial museum in India, Birla Industrial and Technological Museum (BITM) is one of the prime attractions of Kolkata and is located on the Gurusaday Road. The museum was set up on 2nd May 1959 and opened to the general public. It was initially known as Birla Park and within three years of its opening was converted into a museum. The palatial structure of museum has led to it becoming a famous tourist attraction famous for its galleries and 3D shows organized in the premises.\n\nBirla Park was transformed into BITM under the influence of Dr B.C. Roy, who in the year 1956 felt that a developing nation like India needed museums in its vicinity. Therefore, the property was handed over to Pandit Jawaharlal Nehru by G.D. Birla to set up the museum which took nearly three years to complete. BITM is also the pioneer of the Mobile Science Exhibition which was the first exhibition on wheels. With its galleries, diverse activities and the growing chains of the satellite centres, this museum is now the place where science manifests itself through means of interactive and animated models. It is an amazing place and a must-visit for all the science lovers out there!</string>
    <string name="rabindra_sarovar">The erstwhile Dhakuria Lake is an artificial tank in South Kolkata. Spread over 75 acres, it is home to varied migratory birds from Siberia and Russia. The lake is home to many fish. Surrounded by gardens, children\'s park and auditorium, this location has been developed over the years to encourage community and welfare. It is a popular recreational spot for idyllic picnics.</string>
    <string name="kalighat_temple">Kalighat Temple is located in Kolkata, West Bengal. One of the 51 Shakti Sthals of India, it is one of the most visited Kali temples in India. The spot is where the toes of Sati\'s right foot fell during Shiva\'s Tandava dance. It is said that Kalighat was where Chowranga Giri, a Dasanami monk, worshipped Ma Kali with great austerity and has thus been known as a religious centre for Ma Kali worship for centuries. This 200-year-old temple embodies the principle that only divine knowledge can subsume sodomized ego, akin to an Asura. This transcendence will lead to moksha, as Ma Kali guides all through their devoted worship of her.</string>
    <string name="shobabazar_rajbari">The Shobhabazar Rajbari is one of the grandest Bengali style houses ever built. It was build by the Royal family of Shobhabazar in Kolkata, and the grandeur is only palpable to the eye.</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden">The Acharya Jagadish Chandra Bose Indian Botanic Garden, better known as the Botanical Garden, is a sprawling garden spanning a total area of 273 acres that is located in Shibpur, Howrah, near Kolkata. The gardens were established in the year 1787 and were commonly known as the Company Garden in that time. It is presently under the Botanical Survey of India (BSI) of Ministry of Environment and Forests, Government of India. Today, the vibrant garden is considered to be one of the most stunning landscaped gardens in the entire country with undulating land topography and astonishing artificial lakes. It is a pure delight for nature lovers to visit this area and to spend some quiet and peaceful time in the lap of nature at the gardens.\n\nThe Botanical Garden boasts of being home to 12,000 living perennial plants as well as thousands of dried out plants which have been collected from all across the globe. Thousands of astounding orchids and multicoloured flowers can also be found in the garden. The major attraction of the garden, however, is the vast and widespread Banyan tree, which is popularly known as the Great Banyan Tree. This enormous tree is reputed for forming the second most extensive canopy in the entire world. The Botanical Gardens were originally founded in 1786 by Colonel Kyd, and are the oldest botanical garden that can be found in the whole country. In fact, the tea that now grows in Assam and Darjeeling was first developed in these gardens.</string>
    <string name="nakhoda_mosque">Placed in the Chitpur area in the Burrabazar business district, Nakhoda mosque is one of the busiest Mosques of Kolkata and dates back almost a century. The prayer hall has a seating capacity of 10000, and the domes and minarets have been constructed in keeping with the Fatehpur Sikri style of architecture.</string>
    <string name="alipore_zoo">The Alipore Zoo, also known as the Calcutta Zoo or the Zoological Garden of Alipore, is the oldest zoological park to have been established in India and is a major tourist attraction in Kolkata, West Bengal. The Alipore Zoo attracts tourists from all across the nation who visit the zoo to explore the wildlife that thrives here. \n\nThe Alipore Zoo is perhaps the most known for being the home of the expired Aldabra giant tortoise \'Adwaita\', a tortoise who had lived for over 250 years before he died in the year 2006. The place is a must-visit for nature enthusiasts, or for families with children, to explore the abundant and plentiful wildlife of the country at its best. Spread over an area of 46.5 acres, the zoo has been operating since 1876, when it was first opened to the general public.\n\nThe Alipore Zoo becomes especially crowded during the winter seasons when tourists flock to this popular destination in Kolkata in huge numbers. Modernisation of the zoo, including the addition of new glass-walled enclosures and building of aviaries, has further led to an increase in the popularity of this zoo.</string>
    <string name="sabarna_sangrahashala">Designed, developed and maintained by Sabarrna Roy Choudhary Paribar Parishad to preserve and display the heritage of one of the well known families of Bengal- The Sabarna Roy Choudhary family.\n\nThe museum exihibits a grand collection rare articles and historical documents dating back to 18th century.</string>
    <string name="eco_tourism_park">Eco-Tourism Park in Kolkata is an expansive urban park designed to promote eco-tourism in the city. It is the biggest urban park in India and occupies over 475 acres of land. The beauty of the location increases ten folds because of a water body that surrounds the park and forms an island in the middle. It is often visited by picnickers or those who want a quick escape from mundane lives. The beautiful and well-maintained landscape is a perfect retreat for nature lovers. All the facilities provided inside the park are designed to decrease the adverse effects on nature through non-pollution and preservation of the natural landscape.\n\nThe idea of an Eco-Tourism Park in Kolkata was proposed by Mamata Banerjee, the Chief Minister of the state of West Bengal. HIDCO - Housing Infrastructure Development Corporation of West Bengal coordinated with several departments and brought about the construction of the Eco-Tourism Park in Kolkata. It has three major parts - the ecological zones, the gardens and the recreational zones making it a perfect getaway to relax and unwind. They have some activities that visitors can choose from to suit their requirement. They also have cottages and conference halls that can be rented for personal or business needs. The Eco Park is a beautiful respite from the developing concrete jungle in the city.</string>
    <string name="pareshnath_jain_temple">Pareshnath Jain Temple is a temple complex dedicated to four Jain Teerthankaras. The complex is a beautiful arrangement of these shrines and draws tourists from all over the world. The architecture of the temples consists of intricately carved marbles and glass work and is indeed one of the few temples that have a charismatic vibe. The complex expands over a vast piece of land and is mostly visited by followers of Jainism. The temple complex also houses extremely well-maintained gardens and fountains. Many visitors claim it is not just a religious retreat but also a recreational one because of its architecture.\n\nPareshwanath Temple complex houses a shop where tourists can purchase souvenirs and gifts. One may choose to offer prayers or pay respect to the Tirthankaras in all the temples. Devotees and the temple management ensure complete silence is maintained and that helps devotees enter a quiet and peaceful zone to meditate. The temples are often crowded in the evenings when visitors come to enjoy the vibe, offer their prayers and feed the birds in the garden area. This is one of the attractions that must not be missed when exploring Kolkata.</string>
    <string name="nicco_park">Nicco Park is an amusement park frequently visited for entertainment and recreational purposes. It is also called the \"Disney Land of West Bengal\" and attracts visitors in large numbers throughout the year. The park functions efficiently on solar energy that causes no pollution. Every aspect of the rides here is appropriately explained at the beginning for the visitors to learn. So, one will find charts and boards displayed at the entrance of every ride illustrating the principles used to ensure a safe and fun ride. The park has numerous amusement rides and shows which are not just recreational but educational also. It is, therefore, a favourite amongst parent and youngsters who often prefer the attraction as a picnic spot.\n\nNicco Park has been functioning as an amusement park for the past 20 years. It is the first amusement park in India that has obtained recognition from Quality Management System, Safety Management System and Environment Management System. Nicco Park is also the first amusement park in the world to have obtained a \'Social Accountability\' certificate. Those looking for an entertaining, educational and a recreational escape must head to the Nicco Park.</string>
    <string name="princep_ghat">Prinsep Ghat, located on the banks of River Hooghly, is a majestic structure famous for its Greek/ Gothic inlays. The beauty of Princep Ghat draws architecture and history buffs in large numbers, but even locals visit to absorb the regal vibe of the attraction. With the magnificent Howrah Bridge in the background, watching the sunrise or sunset and taking a long walk in the cool air on the banks of the river are some of the preferred recreational activities here.\n\nDuring the British Rule, it was used by the staff of the British Royals as a jetty for loading and unloading passengers and essential items. The ghat is located between Fort William and the Water Gate and is often visited by tourists exploring these attractions. Prinsep Ghat is one of the few locations that have been restored to maintain the pre-independence aura. It is, therefore, a favourite amongst photographers especially for pre-wedding shoots. In between exploring the attraction, if one feels like grabbing a bite, there are several food kiosks to choose from that serve scrumptious local snacks. Prinsep Ghat is sure to be the highlight of one’s trip to Kolkata.</string>
    <string name="aquatica">Aquatica is a water theme park and resort in Kolkata having many exciting themed rides, slides, entertainment and recreational activities for all their guests. The water park occupies over 75000 square feet of area and provides for a pleasant respite from the scorching summer heat. They provide lockers for the visitors to keep their belongings securely. With many rides one can choose from, the young and the old, both are bound to find something to suit their requirement. Whether one wants to laze around in the pool or go for a thrilling water slide, there\'s something for everyone here. In between the ride, if one feels a need for a snack they can head to the restaurant that serves a variety of local and international cuisine.\n\nThe Aquatica Resort has all facilities and amenities to make their guests stay comfortable and memorable. They have luxurious rooms to accommodate solo travellers and families. 24x7 room service, parking services, free Wi-Fi etc. are some of the facilities they provide. Aquatica is also a favourite venue for events like birthdays, weddings, engagement parties, anniversary parties, team outings and award ceremonies. They also arrange for live shows and corporate events on a grand level to ensure the guests have a fabulous time. It is a perfect picnic attraction to spend a day having fun with the family.</string>
    <string name="park_street">Park Street is a major access route in Kolkata, also officially known as Mother Teresa Sarani. The street begins at Chowringhee Road or JL Nehru road and stretches till Park Circus crossing. It is said that Park Street never sleeps and is always bustling with activities. Being a major hangout spot in the city, it has many pubs and restaurants. Several important routes intersect or originate from Park Street. The street has been a crowd puller since the reign of the British Kingdom and undergone modifications that make it a fashionable hangout spot.\n\nPark Street is one area in the city where one will find 5-Star restaurant and hotels, nightclubs/pubs, malls and several eateries. The street draws locals in large numbers on the occasions of Diwali, Christmas and New Year\'s Eve. The entire street is decorated with bright and colourful lights celebrating the festivals with great enthusiasm. A number of prominent landmarks are also located in or near Park Street. Some of them are Asiatic Society, St. Xavier\'s College, South Park Street Cemetery and The Park Hotel. It is one of the prime entertainment and recreational zone in Kolkata.</string>
    <string name="chowringhee">Chowringhee, officially known as Jawaharlal Nehru Road, is a happening hub and frequently visited by locals for recreational activities and shopping. It is one of the few localities in the city with top end boutiques, hotels, malls, shops and restaurants. The region also has several heritage buildings nearby that tourists can explore. These buildings were built during the British era and are famous for their architecture and historical importance that photographers shouldn\'t miss at all.\n\nChowringhee was the inspiration of a novelist from Bengal, Sankar which was also featured in a movie made in 1968. It is one of the places for the night owls searching for nightclubs/ pubs. With the Chowringhee Market nearby, the area is a paradise for shopaholics. It also houses some main metro stations in the city. Due to its accessibility, locals visit the area often to explore on foot or window shop or indulge in some delicious street feed. It does get very crowded during peak hours, but there\'s something for everyone here at Chowringhee.</string>
    <string name="iskcon">ISKCON Radha Krishna Temple is a highly spiritual place for the devotees. The temple is also called Sri Sri Radha Govind Mandir and mainly focuses on spreading the teachings of Lord Krishna. It is not restricted to any one particular religion as such and welcomes enthusiasts or people interested in learning about these teachings with open arms. The temple is a serene complex that houses beautifully ornamented idols of Goddess Radha and Lord Krishna. The complex is very well maintained and provides for a serene atmosphere for devotees to soak in the heavenly vibes of the deities.\n\nISKCON was founded by A.C.Bhaktivedanta Swami Prabhupada in 1966 in New York to open up the world to the valuable teachings of Lord Krishna based on the sacred Hindu scriptures of Bhagwad Geeta and Bhagwad Purana. This spiritual path introduces people to the Sanatana Dharma and Vedic Culture and helps them live a stress-free life. Visitors can also enjoy a 100% vegetarian sattvic meal that is prepared by the volunteers in clean and hygienic conditions. Most of the devotees visit the temple to clear their minds of endless chatter and to purify their souls through the chanting of the \'Hare Rama\' mantra. To witness the vibe when the mantra is chanted by all the devotees is a surreal experience.</string>
    <string name="south_park_street_cementry">South Park Street Cemetery is an 18th-century non-church cemetery, one of the earliest in the world. It is now a heritage site in Kolkata and maintained by the Archaeological Survey of India. Most of the tombs in the South Park Street Cemetery are aesthetically beautiful and very attractive. It, thus, has a unique charm that draws tourists in large numbers. Some tombs have a mysterious while some have a soothing vibe. One such tomb is grave number 363 which is the oldest and belongs to a woman who never wished to have her name revealed. The tomb architecture is mostly a mix of Gothic and Indo-Saracenic with miniature replicas on stone.\n\nThe cemetery was opened in 1767 on a marshland to take off some load of the old Burial Ground in Kolkata. The location has also been featured in several Bengali and Tollywood movies like Gorosthaney Sabdhan, which is a movie based on a novel written by Satyajit Ray. The cemetery is very well-maintained and has spacious pavilions lined with tall green trees and monuments for the dead. South Park Street Cemetery has a melancholic charm that cannot be missed. If one wishes to pay their respects or just explore this heritage site must visit the South Park Street Cemetery.</string>
    <string name="sonajhuri_forest">Away from the mell pell of the city lies a hidden gem in the state of West Bengal. Considered to be one of the most clean forests in India, Sonajhuri Forest is a great retreat to be close to nature. The Sonajhuri Forest is replete with lush green trees that has blooming flowers. This place is picturesque with quite a number of mesmerizing places to see and explore. This place is untouched by industrialization and is a inhabited by tribal who lead simple lives. The pristine river flowing alongside the forest makes the whole place look even more magical. Just like Tagore, after seeing its beauty, this place might invoke the poet in you.</string>
    <string name="st_john_church">St John\'s Church is one of the oldest churches in Kolkata that was built during the reign of the British Kingdom when the city was the capital of British India. The church served as Anglican Cathedral till St. Paul\'s Cathedral was made the Anglican cathedral in 1847. It is a splendidly well-maintained structure that draws history and architecture buffs for its uniqueness and ancient features. One may notice the unique tall features of St John\'s Church which is a characteristic part of the neoclassical architecture. The colour scheme and the stained glass windows add to the character of the structure. The church maintains utmost silence to allow the visitors to sit in peace for at least a moment.\n\nThe regal edifice was built on land which once was used as a graveyard so that visitors will find a lot of memorials and tombs in the compound. Each of these memorials or tombs is a piece of art and history that make some mourn while they inspire some. These stories not just offer a glimpse into the melancholic stage of human beings, but also force us to appreciate the present and inspire us to make our lives even better. St John\'s Church is a perfect attraction for those who wish to immerse themselves in the divine powers of the God or those who are always searching for a spiritual escape in the city. Visiting the church is a blissful experience in itself.</string>
    <string name="barrackpore">Barrackpore was the first place where Britishers set up their cantonment and later spread their rules in India. This place is of great historical significance as it was also the first place where the spark to attain I from Britishers was lit. Not to stop at that, this place is also home to some of the most mesmerizing and green parks which are perfect to spend some time lazing around? and relaxing. Pristine temples are also situated in Barrackpore that will purge you soul and invite positive vibes. A visit to Barrackpore will let you enjoy some calm away from the hustle bustle of the city and also give knowledge about one of the most important chapters in the history of India.</string>
    <string name="jhargram">Jhargram is small city located in the state of West Bengal with a rich historical and cultural background. Surrounded by dense forests this place is mystical. A perfect place to spend few days in the lap of nature surrounded by friendly tribal population, you are bound to be mesmerized not only by its picturesque beauty but by the gregarious people who inhabit this place. The chirpings of birds will make your heart swell with happiness and you will feel as if you are in paradise.</string>
    <string name="baabur_haat">Babur haat is the perfect weekend destination for you and your loved ones if you do wish to take a break from the hectic city life and spend some time close to rustic Bengali rural life. Dominated by natural fishing lakes or bheris, responsible for producing some of the tastiest fish in West Bengal, Babur Haat is a nature paradise. Long stretches rice farmlands, vegetable orchards, mango groves, palm groves and rural homes and temples make a wonderful scenic landscape. Fishing is one of the more popular activities in Babur Haat. You can also go on a short picnic trip to the nearby local village grounds, open spaces of which also allow for outdoor games like badminton and cricket to be played. Malancha villages, famous for its fish markets is only 15 km from Babur Haat. You can also opt for country boating, by crossing the river to visit Chaital village. Greenery, fresh air and open spaces will definitely leave your spirits rejuvenated. Babur Haat is located at a distance of about 50 km from Kolkata. You can also choose to avail the bus services from Kolkata to Malancha village via Babur Haat.</string>
    <string name="kamarpukur">A cluster of small villages, Kamarpukur is nestled between Vishnupur and Tarakeshwar. Birthplace of a pious and sagacious saint, Sri Ramkrishna Paramhansa, this village is perfect getaway from the pell-mell of the cities. In this village you will be able to enjoy the pleasures of simple rural life. This place being pious is filled with positivity and you will feel recharged after visiting it. Replete with temples and scenic beauty this is just the place to unwind from the pressure of all the deadlines that you are struggling to meet.</string>
    <string name="deulti">Situated on the bank of river Roopnarayan, Deulti provides for an ideal picnic spot. This small village picnic destination is also accompanied by a handful of tourist attractions, like Samtaber, the hometown of renowned Bengali author Sarat Chandra Chattopadhyay and the temples of Madangopal and Radha, adorned with embellishments of Terracotta art. If you are a bird lover, keep an eye (read ear) for the chirps of different birds, while you take a walk on the clay paths of the villages. Other popular townships like Kolaghat, Garchumuk and Gadiara are also located nearby Deulti. If you travel by car, Deulti is situated at a distance of about 51 km from Howrah. Alternately, you can avail train services from Howrah station to Deulti station.</string>
    <string name="hooghly_riverfront">The very picturesque Hooghly Riverfront is situated along two banks of River Hooghly in West Bengal- Kolkata in the East and Howrah on the West. The mighty river offers mesmerising sunrise and sunset views. After the beautification of the East promenade in 2011, the spot has become a major tourist attraction.</string>
    <string name="maidan">Also known as the Brigade Parade Ground, Maidan is the largest urban park in Kolkata. The humongous stretch of land includes the famous Eden Gardens, several football stadiums and the Race Course Kolkata.</string>
    <string name="central_park">Also known as Banabitan, Central Park is the second largest urban park after Maidan, situated in Bidhannagar, Kolkata. Built around an expansive lake, the park also has a rose garden which has umpteen varieties of domestic and imported roses. Another attraction in the Central Park is its beautiful butterfly garden which is home to several species of colorful butterflies.</string>
    <string name="millenium_park">Spread over an area of 2.5 kms on the banks of River Hooghly in Kolkata, Millennium Park is a privately owned park situated on the Strand Road. The park has beautiful landscaped gardens and numerous slides and swings for kids.</string>
    <string name="deshapriyo_park">Deshapriya Park is situated in the Kalighat area of South Kolkata and is used for playing outdoor games like cricket, football etc., both by amateur and professional players. In addition to that, Durga Puja is celebrated on a large scale where several pandals are set up in the premises for the celebrations.</string>
    <string name="safari_park">Situated near Gariahat Golpark, Safari Park is one of the relatively smaller parks in Kolkata. The park also has a lake on the outskirts that is ideal for early morning walks and evening strolls. A smaller area on the side is also used as a cricket coaching for young kids. The park is buzzing with activity at all times of the day.</string>
    <string name="mohor_kunja">Also known as Citizen\'s Park, Mohor Kunja is an urban park in Kolkata situated in the premises of Maidan. The highlight of the park are the several musical fountain concerts held in it. It also has well-paved walkways for evening and morning walks and an amphitheater to hold cultural events.</string>
    <string name="elliot_park">Inaugurated in 2004, Elliot Park is one of the relatively newer parks to have been developed in the city. The park has a joggers stretch of 1.5 km besides the lush green vegetation, swings for children and water fountains.</string>
    <string name="gitanjali_sports_complex">Located at Kasba in Kolkata, Gitanjali Sports Complex is the newly established stadium in the city. Running for a length of 57.5 metres, the stadium has a massive seating space for 4000 people. Besides, it has a separate area for indoor games and a gymnasium.</string>
    <string name="kishore_bharati">Kishore Bharati Krirangan is a multi purpose stadium situated in the south Kolkata neighbourhood of Santoshpur. With a seating capacity of 12000 people, the stadium is mostly used for football and sometimes other sports as well.</string>
    <string name="salt_lake_stadium">Known as Vivekananda Yuva Bharati Krirangan, Salt Lake Stadium is an international multi-purpose stadium in Bidhannagar, Kolkata. The stadium takes pride in being the largest stadium of the country, it can accommodate up to 1,20,000 people.</string>
    <string name="rabindra_sarovar_stadium">Rabindra Sarobar Stadium is situated in the centre of the city of Kolkata in Rabindra Sarovar. Believed to be the oldest stadiums of the city, the stadium has a seating capacity of 20,000 people and host some of the important football matches.</string>
    <string name="mohunbagan_stadium">Mohunbagan Stadium is the oldest and the first stadium in the country. It is also the place of inception of the very famous Mohunbagan Club. The stadium is considered the best in Kolkata as its emerald green grass cover is imported from Brazil.</string>
    <string name="netaji_indoor_stadium">Officially named as Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose Indoor Stadium, Netaji Indoor Stadium is a multi-purpose indoors stadium in Babughat, Kolkata, opposite the Eden Gardens. The fully air-conditioned stadium is used to host various domestic and international events.</string>
    <string name="barasat_stadium">Also known as Vidyasagar Krirangan, Barasat Stadium is a football stadium located in Barasat in Kolkata. The stadium is mostly used for CFL and I-League matches and has a seating capacity of 22,000 spectators.</string>
    <string name="east_bengal_ground">East Bengal Ground is the home stadium of the East Bengal Football Club and can accommodate up to 23,500 people. The stadium also has a natural grass cover. Additional facilities include commentary boxes, radio box, ac changing rooms and a gym.</string>
    <string name="kolkata_race_course">Built in 1820, Kolkata Race Course is the largest horse racing venue in the country. Maintained by Royal Calcutta Turf Club, the stadium hosts races in the months of July to September, and between November to March.</string>
    <string name="nalban_boating_park">Nalban Boating Park is one of the most popular amusement parks in Kolkata situated in Bidhannagar. The beautiful green park is divided into three zones- ecological zones, theme gardens and recreational spaces; and it also facilitates boating in the lake situated within the premises.</string>
    <string name="snow_park">Snow Park is situated within the Axis Mall in Newtown Kolkata and is a beautiful rendition of an amusement park covered in white snow flakes. It is especially popular among the city dwellers who do not experience real snow fall ever in the plain area. The park also has thrilling rides for both the kids and adults.</string>
    <string name="wet_o_wild">Wet-O-Wild aka the Pirates Bay is a widely popular theme amusement cum water park situated in Salt Lake City in Kolkata. It draws the maximum number of visitors during the summers. However, even in the winter season, the park attracts tourists coming to relax or sun soak in the appealing deer park situated within the premises.</string>
    <string name="genesis_art_gallery">Genesis Art Gallery is situated on the Middleton Street in Kolkata and has been popular for more than 30 years now for its exhibitions and displays on contemporary arts. Besides the Indian artists, the gallery also encourages international talent and art works. Among the most prominent names of the gallery are Rameshwa Broota, Suhas Roy, and Sunil Das.</string>
    <string name="galerie_88">Galerie 88 is a renowned gallery in Kolkata promoting modern and contemporary art. It hosts exhibitions displaying artworks of both the domestic and international stalwarts. The most noted artists celebrated in the gallery include MF Hussain, Ganesh Pyne, Paritosh Sen, SG Vasudev etc.</string>
    <string name="experimenter_art_gallery">Experimenter Art Gallery is situated in Ballygunge, Kolkata and is one of the finest contemporary galleries in the city. Besides it encourages and promotes young and budding artists. Among the most notable artists are Bani Adibi, Adip Dutta, Sanchayan Ghosh etc. They also host an annual event called \'Curator\'s Hub\' every year in July.</string>
    <string name="masters_collections_art_gallery">Situated in Woodburn Park Road, Kolkata, Masters Collection Art Gallery was started with the objective to curate and display the artworks of the \'Old Masters\' from the 12th to the 20th Century. But lately, the gallery has shifted their expertise to modern and contemporary arts. It organizes regular exhibitions showcasing works of eminent artists from all around the world.</string>
    <string name="verandah_art_gallery">Situated in Bhowanipore in Kolkata, Verandah Art Gallery is a quaint boutique style gallery featuring artworks from contemporary artists. Ranging from realistic, figurative, abstract, surreal and experimental works, the gallery promotes and encourages young and budding artists.</string>
    <string name="chitrakoot_art_gallery">Chitrakoot Art Gallery is situated in Ballygunge in Kolkata and is the oldest commercial gallery in the city. The gallery is renowned for exhibiting art works of very many stalwarts so much so that it was frequently visited by M.F.Hussain also. The gallery also has a photography exhibit, an art library, a restoration department, and an art valuation consultancy.</string>
    <string name="akar_prakar_gallery">Akar Prakar is another one of the renowned galleries situated in Gariahat in Kolkata. Originally the gallery started out at a furniture outlet in Jaipur. In 1992, it was moved to Kolkata and it started hosting \'media shows\' showcasing contemporary and modern artworks.</string>
    <string name="aakriti_art_gallery">Situated in the Park Street area in Kolkata, Aakriti Art Gallery focuses on the contemporary and modern artists, promoting and showcasing the talents of young and budding visionaries. It frequently hosts the GenNext exhibition to exhibit the young talents. It also has two wings - one for paintings and photographs, and the other for sculptures.</string>
    <string name="chemould_art_gallery">Chemould Art Gallery is a big name with its counterpart in Mumbai. Claiming to be one of the oldest galleries in India, it was founded by Mr. Keekoo Gandhy in 1941. It hosts various exhibitions to honour the prominent artists. The gallery is also believed to have mentored people like M F Husain, Tyeb Mehta, Ram Kumar, and SH Raza.</string>
    <string name="janus_art_gallery">Situated on the Upen Banerjee Road in Kolkata, Janus Art Gallery is a unique gallery featuring collections from \'Old Master\' meaning the old-age artists, line paintings, abstract paintings, contemporary paintings and sculptures. It also promotes the young and budding artists and the gallery can only be visited on prior appointment.</string>
    <string name="harrington_street_art_centre">Harrington Street Arts Centre is situated on the Ho Chi Minh Sarani Road in Kolkata and is also known as the resource centre for diverse art forms. The gallery specializes in curating and presenting the artworks of contemporary artists both local and international.</string>
    <string name="cima_gallery">CIMA Gallery Pvt Ltd is one of the big names when it comes to modern art. The gallery displays the artworks of famous masters and also young budding artists. The highlight of the gallery is the annual Art Mela held every October annually. The take-away paintings are a treasure and are really reasonably priced.</string>
    <string name="magen_david_synagogue">Megan David Synagogue is situated in China Bazaar, Kolkata and was constructed in 1884. The building is build in red brick in the Italian Renaissance style. It is among the most notable buildings of Calcutta owing to its striking architecture and design.</string>
    <string name="beth_el_synagogue">Beth El Synagogue is situated at Barabazar Market in Kolkata, very close to the Maghen David Synagogue. Established in 1856, the building has marble steps leading to the arched hallway. The walls are adorned with stained glass windows. The hall also has balconies reserved for women.</string>
    <string name="neveh_shalome_synagogue">Neveh Shalome Synagogue is situated in China Bazar in Kolkata and was established in 1831 by Shalom Obadiah ha - Kohen. The synagogue was demolished and reconstructed multiple times by the government and the Indian Jewish community. It was finally restored in 2014. Now it has simple but elegant interiors, and conducts regular prayers.</string>
    <string name="trams_in_kolkata">Trams are an inherent part of the culture and history of Kolkata. Although their numbers are now diminished, they are still far from extinct, and a trip to Kolkata does not seem complete without a tram car ride across the city. Today, it is the only tram system in India, and quite possibly the only one of its kind in Asia. Tram routes run parallel to other vehicles on special tracks laid out along the side of the busy streets. They follow the whims of the traffic lights and are akin to miniature local trains. The rusty trams maintain the very vintage charm and are equipped with a TV and FM radio. Although it was originally an important medium of transport, the trams have lately become really popular with tourists. When in the City of Joy, do not forget to enjoy a dainty tram ride across town.</string>
    <string name="mousuni_island">Mousuni is a tiny island which is attached to the Sunderbans Delta near Namkhana in West Bengal. Boasting of golden sandy shores, mesmerising orange sunsets and a beautiful view of the horizon, the island was first developed by the British to trade salt and dry fish. Considered to be a paradise among the nature lovers because of its serenity and tranquility, the island is a beautiful confluence of the river and the sea.\n\nIn addition to the exceptional natural beauty and gorgeous panoramic vistas, the Mousuni Island is a well kept secret of the state and is known by few which explains the peace and calm at the place. It is also considered to be a bird watchers paradise since a lot of birds migrate here for the winter. It also has a number of activities to offer to the tourists that include beach cycling, volleyball, idling and sun soaking etc. There are also several camps at the beach where you can spend the night.</string>
    <string name="dakshineswar_kali">Flanked by River Hooghly on the Eastern bank, Dakshineswar Kali is a revered Hindu navratna temple which is presided by Bhavatarini - a form of Goddess Kali. Built in Rani Rashmoni in 1855 who was a devotee of Goddess Kali, the Bhavatarini form means \‘she, who liberates her devotees from the ocean of existence.\’ Aside from the main shrine, there are also several rooms built along the complex surrounding the boundary walls.\n\nIn these rooms, there are shrines dedicated to several gods. 12 of these are dedicated to Lord Shiva, 1 to Radha Krishna, and 1 to Rani Rashmoni. In addition to that, there is also a bathing ghat on the river. Besides, the temple is also known for its famous association with Sri Ramakrishna who was a yogi, mystic and a revered person of the 19th century Bengal. Other than paying your respect to the gods and goddesses, you can also admire the gorgeous architectural designs and beautiful scenic beauty.</string>
    <string name="ramkrishnapur_ghat">Ramkrishnapur Ghat is one of the ancient ghats in Kolkata, built along the banks of Ganga River. This beautiful and enchanting ghat is surrounded by a series of beautifully constructed ancient temples and staircases running towards the banks where one of the most beautiful Ganga Aarti takes place. While Varanasi and Haridwar are famous for its grand Ganga Aartis, Ramkrishnapur Ghat offers its own spin on it. Right from harmonious chanting of mantras, colourful flowers, grand Aarti Thaal (brass lamps) and a massive crowd of devoted attendees, all is seen here. The vibes are such that even with such a large number of devotees present, one\'s soul will be satisfied.</string>
    
    // Data for RestaurantActivity.java
    <string name="barbeque_nation">Location:-\nDiamond Plaza Mall, Jessore Road\n\nCuisine:-\nMulticuisine Barbeque\n\nTime:-\n12:00pm - 4:00pm and 6:00pm - 11:30pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="reloaded_pied_pipers">Location:-\nKasba, Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nMulticuisine\n\nTime:-\n11:00am - 11:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="vintage_asia">Location:-\nJW Marriott Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nChinese Thai Multicuisine Pan Asian\n\nTime:-\n12:30pm - 2:45pm and 7:00pm - 9:30pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="six_ballygunge_place">Location:-\nBallygunge, Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nBangladeshi Bengali Beverages Desearts\n\nTime:-\n12:00pm - 4:00pm and 7:00pm - 10:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="rendezvous">Location:-\nMonotel Luxury Business Hotel, Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nMulticuisine\n\nTime:-\n7:00am - 10:30am, 12:00pm - 3:00pm and 7:00pm - 9:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="alfresco">Location:-\nThe Lalit Great Eastern Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nMulticuisine\n\nTime:-\n12:00pm - 9:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="zen">Location:-\nThe Park, Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nPan Asian\n\nTime:-\n7:00am - 10:30pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="the_bridge">Location:-\nThe Park, Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nMulticuisine\n\nTime:-\n12:00pm - 10:30pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="mirage">Location:-\nThe Stadel, Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nMulticuisine\n\nTime:-\n3:00pm - 10:30pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="orkos_restaurant">Location:-\nRegenta Orkos Kolkata, Kasba\n\nCuisine:-\nMulticuisine\n\nTime:-\n12:00pm - 9:30pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="fatty_bao">Location:-\nCamac Street Area, Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nSushi Pan Asian\n\nTime:-\n12:00pm - 9:30pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="the_square">Location:-\nNovotel, Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nMulticuisine\n\nTime:-\n12:00pm - 11:59pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="the_bakery">Location:-\nThe Lalit Great Eastern Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nCafe\n\nTime:-\n7:00am - 10:30pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="chili_grill_and_bar">Location:-\nAcropolis Mall, Kasba\n\nCuisine:-\nAmerican Finger Food Mexican Tex-Mex\n\nTime:-\n12:00pm - 12:00am (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="asia_kitchen">Location:-\nAcropolis Mall, Kasba\n\nCuisine:-\nChinese Finger Food Sushi Pan Asian Asian\n\nTime:-\n12:30pm - 3:30am and 7:00pm - 11:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="oh_calcutta">Location:-\nForum Mall, Elgin\n\nCuisine:-\nBengali Finger Food\n\nTime:-\n12:30pm - 3:30am and 7:00pm - 11:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="jw_kitchen">Location:-\nJW Marriott Kolkata\n\nCuisine:-\nEuropean Finger Food Healthy Food Juices, Mediterranean Indian Thai Multicuisine, Continental Salad\n\nTime:-\n12:30pm - 3:30am and 7:00pm - 10:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="fly_kouzina">Location:-\nSector 1, Salt Lake\n\nCuisine:-\nBeverages, Chinese, Desserts, Italian, North Indian, Pizza, Kababs, Multicuisine\n\nTime:-\n12:00pm - 10:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="mainland_china">Location:-\nSouth City Mall, Prince Anwar Shah Road\n\nCuisine:-\nBeverages, Chinese Finger Food, Seafood\n\nTime:-\n12:30pm - 3:30pm and 7:00pm - 11:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>
    <string name="cafe_mezzuna">Location:-\nSouth City Mall, Prince Anwar Shah Road\n\nCuisine:-\nEuropean\n\nTime:-\n12:30pm - 11:00pm (Monday - Sunday)</string>

    // Data for CuisineActivity.java
    <string name="macher_jhol">There is no doubt that both rice and fish are the staple Kolkata cuisines. Every restaurant with a Bengali food menu has the famous Macher Jhol. While this traditional dish is a spicy fish curry made along with potatoes &amp; tomatoes, and usually seasoned with turmeric, garlic, onions &amp; grated ginger, it is best relished with rice. If you\’re a seafood lover, make sure this is on the top of your list.</string>
    <string name="kolkata_biryani">Inspired by the Awadhi style, the Kolkata Biryani is a heart winner! It\’s captivating aroma and the finely flavoured rice with potato cooked in rich spices is served hot with juicy mutton or chicken, which makes it a must-have when you\’re in the city. If you\’re not an experimental kind of a foodie, and wish to bet safe, rest assured and order this one from the menu.</string>
    <string name="kosa_mangsho">One of the famous Bengali food recipes, Kosha Mangsho is a curry cooked with mutton, a variety of vegetables like tomatoes and onions, and topped with a lot of different spices. It\’s dense brown color adds on to the feel, and there is no denying that it tastes like heaven, especially if one is a meat lover. To make the most out of it, you can savour it with steamed rice, luchis, or paranthas. This is amongst the most famous food of Kolkata.</string>
    <string name="alor_tarkari_luchi">While it may come across as our usual aloo poori from the North India, know that it is not. With potatoes cooked in a thick tomato gravy, this scrumptious curry is the safest Kolkata food to try in the city. Served mostly with breads like luchi or chapati, it is an ideal toothsome snack to have for breakfast.</string>
    <string name="shukto">Counted as one of the best Bengali vegetarian recipes, Shukto is a traditional cuisine that consists of a variety of vegetables like potato, pumpkin, bottle gourd, bitter gourd, and more. Its partly bitter and partly sweet taste makes it a unique concoction, which can be had along with rice or a traditional flat bread.</string>
    <string name="chelo_kebab">If you\’re a hardcore chicken lover, this platter of mutton seekhs and chicken kebabs is one thing you must definitely try in Kolkata. Served along with steamed rice and veggies, it is an exceptionally lip-smacking cuisine and can be enjoyed both as a starter or in the main course.</string>
    <string name="mochar_ghonto">This is one of the most famous household dishes in Kolkata which is a traditional add-on at every Bengali restaurant and home. Made with banana flower and grated coconut, this vegetarian tastes heavenly with rice. The meaning of \“Mocha\” in Bengali is flower which is cleaned properly and requires a lot of time and patience. After removing the petals, the flower is pressure cooked and later the spices are added to give a relishing flavor.</string>
    <string name="katla_kalia">The Katla Kalia is a traditional delicacy which is made of 3 kg weighed Katla fish. This dish holds quite an importance in a bengali household. Cooked with onions, bay leaf, ginger and garlic paste which is further curd with spices, garam masala and ghee. This is one of the most preferred dishes for a Sunday lunch.</string>
    <string name="macher_murir_ghonto">This is another traditional bengali dish and its recipe has been passed down by generation after generation. The Macher Muri Ghonto is made of Rohu fish and the gravy is made of onion, chili, cumin paste, ginger paste which adds all the authentic flavor to this ancient recipe. This fish dish is served with white rice and makes a delicious delicacy to enjoy in the city.</string>
    <string name="aloo_posto">This is an old traditional delicacy which is served as a side dish in every Bengali household. This is considered as a saviour when the guest comes over surprisingly. Made of poppy seeds and potato, this is the perfect side dish with dal and white rice. In the Bengali cuisine, this is one of the best dishes.</string>
    <string name="puchka">Also known as gol gappas and paani puri, these tiny water-bombs with spicy masala and meethi chutney are one of the best things to have in the streets of Kolkata. While they look light, they are quite filling and toothsome, and that is exactly the reason why you just can’t stop at ones.</string>
    <string name="telebhaja">A famous snack in the city that continues to successfully retain the essence of Bengali cuisine, Telebhaja are best enjoyed in monsoons with a cup of tea. From beguni and phuluri to peyaji and alur chop, these crunchy snacks covered in besan (corn-flour) have something for everyone\’s taste buds.</string>
    <string name="jhalmuri">Amongst the best street food in Kolkata, Jhalmuri is the most perfect snack that you can relish whilst exploring the streets. These look like puffed rice or muri and are mixed along with peanuts, coriander and other spices, which make it an appetizing quick bite.</string>
    <string name="chop">Also known as cutlets in a few parts of North India, Chop is one of the most filling yet delicious snack to have in the city. This Kolkata cuisine is prepared by stuffing alur, prawns, or chicken into a ball made of dough, which is then deep fried for attaining crispiness. You can enjoy it dry or have it served with your favorite chutney and tea!</string>
    <string name="kathi_rolls">Unlike any other ordinary roll, the Kathi Rolls in this city are exceptionally lip-smacking. Egg, mutton, chicken, or paneer, you just name your favorite and you\’ll get it. They are mostly made like a flaky flour paratha, which is further rolled up with the chosen stuffing and is laced with irresistible sauces, spices, and veggies.</string>
    <string name="roshogola">Popular across the states for being the best dessert in the city, Bengali rasgullas are like balls of cottage cheese and semolina dough, which are dipped in a sugary syrup to add sweetness to them. They are best had right after the main course, but it\’s true that if you have been born with a sweet tooth, one just won\’t be enough for you.</string>
    <string name="sondesh">Sandesh is a popular dessert in Kolkata, which is made from milk or cottage cheese and sugar, and is one of the most famous snacks that you would come across in the city. Molded into a variety of shapes like the little balls and circular discs, this doughy and buttery sweet dessert puts a perfect end to our any main course traditional Bengali cuisine.</string>
    <string name="chom_chom">There is quite a high possibility that you may have heard of Chom Chom if you love taking a tour of the sweet shops. Also called as chum chums, this sweet is made of flour, cream, sugar, saffron, lemon juice and, coconut flakes, and is usually served during the festive season.</string>
    <string name="misti_doi">Consisting of a fermented sweet yogurt, Mishti Doi is one of the area\’s most famous culinary delight. While you can also buy packaged mishti doi in grocery stores in your own city today, the fresh ones from Kolkata\’s legendary sweet shops is definitely worth trying at least once.</string>
    <string name="patisapta">This is quite a famous sweet delicacy which is a favorite for every Bengali out there. Patisapta is made during the \‘poush parbon\’ along with other traditional sweet delicacies like Dudh-Puli, Malpua and Kolar Bora. Made of milk and refined flour, this is made in a round shape and stuffed with coconut, dry fruit and mawa and served like a roll.</string>

    // Data for FestivalActivity.java
    <string name="saraswati_puja">Perhaps one of the unique celebrations of Kolkata is the day celebrating the Homecoming of the Hindu Goddess of Learning, Goddess Saraswati. This is usually celebrated on the fifth day of Hindu month of Magha, known as Vasant Panchami in Northern parts of the country and Saraswati Puja in West Bengal predominately. This day is dedicated to the Goddess as a day when all the study related things should have an auspicious beginning. In Kolkata people consider this day to be very fortunate for their children to start writing for the first time. This day is also marked by small girls wearing colourful saris and going out on the streets to visit the richly decorated pandals of Goddess Saraswati.</string>
    <string name="basanti_durga_puja">Although the more known celebration of the Homecoming of Goddess Durga is during the month of September- October, scriptures have it that originally the Puja was performed in the spring season. This form of worship of Goddess Durga was the only time that the Goddess was called upon the earth but nowadays the \'Shardiya Durga Puja\' has become more famous. But the Basanti Durga Puja is still very famous in the Kolkata region. Considering it to be a miniature Durga Puja, the city comes alive with the sound of conch shells and brightly lit pandals with extensively decorated idols of the Goddess and people wearing colourful attires and dancing to the beat of \'dhakis\'.</string>
    <string name="poila_boishakh">Poila Boishakh or the first day of Baisakh is the first day of a Bengali calendar year. The day is often known as Bengali New Year. This day marks the beginning of a new year for a Bengali household and thus calls for a celebration. People make extensive preparations for this day, buying new clothes, preparing extensive dishes at home and most importantly offering prayers to Gods and Goddesses. This day is very special for the Bengalis. On this day the traders start their new accounting books, the ceremony is commonly known as \'Hal Khata\'.</string>
    <string name="jamai_shosti">This beautiful commemoration celebrates the complicated but underrated relationship between a mother in law and her son in law. This is a day to bring the warmth back in the relationships and proves to be yet another reason to celebrate the blessing that is life. On this special day, the son in law visits his in-laws home where a grand party is organized for him, containing people from the household or more acquaintances as they want to mark the occasion. The mother in law cooks extensive and mouth-watering dishes for her son in law and no celebration in the Bengali household can be complete without food. The day is also marked with giving gifts to the son in law from his in-laws too and also being blessed by them with having a long and prosperous life ahead.</string>
    <string name="durga_puja">Perhaps one of the grandest festivals of the state, Durga Puja of Kolkata is famous worldwide for the huge celebrations and the faith that comes with the victory of Good over Evil. The festival is a massive celebration in the name of Goddess Durga who defeated the shape-shifting demon Mahisasura after a ten-day battle. The day is known as Vijay Dashmi. The celebrations are truly on a different level altogether with roads being ten times more crowded than the usual (mind you the usual crowd there is unusually large!)with people going out for their last minute shopping sessions and for sightseeing the extensive pandals that flock the city. The city sure has some of the best artistically made pandals which draw attention from all around the world. The city loses itself during the 10 days of celebration.</string>
    <string name="lakshmi_puja">Lakshmi Puja is the celebration of the homecoming for the Hindu Goddess of wealth and prosperity, Goddess Lakshmi. The festival is entirely restricted to the Bengalis since Hindus apart from Bengalis do this Puja during Diwali - the festival of lights. This is usually done at home by a priest or by own and offerings are made to Goddess Lakshmi and prayers are made to bring wealth and prosperity to their homes.</string>
    <string name="kali_puja">Celebrated nearly twenty days after Durga Puja this festival is perhaps the other largest festival of Kolkata apart from Durga Puja. Celebrated in the honour of Goddess Kali, this festival is marked by chanting mantras during nighttime which goes up till dawn. The Deity is adorned with garlands of hibiscuses and offered sweets, rice and lentils although animal sacrifices are also made at a few places, now has been greatly reduced. The festival is celebrated when the rest of the country celebrates Diwali - the festival of lights.</string>
    <string name="bhai_phota">This festival is celebrated in Kolkata as a substitute for the Hindu Raksha Bandhan although it is somewhat different. In this, the sister puts a \'tika\' on the forehead of her brother while muttering incantations and then feeds him, sweets. The sister prays for the long life of her brother and also that he finds the strength to fight wrongdoings. This is the Bengali version of celebration cherishes the bond between a brother and sister.</string>
    <string name="dover_lane_music_festival">Dover Lane Music Festival is a unique Indian classical music festival that is held annually in the Nazrul Mancha auditorium in Kolkata. The three day long festival is lit from dawn to dusk and invites prominent personalities of classical music from all over the world. Aside from the music stalwarts and high end personalities, young artists and blooming musicians are also encouraged to perform in the festival. Over the years, the festival has gained tremendous popularity and has also earned itself a lot of sponsors. Aside from the cultural music, you can also enjoy the snacks and refreshments from the stalls standing outside.</string>
    <string name="calcutta_book_fair">Now known as the International Kolkata Book Fair, Calcutta Book Fair was first held in Kolkata in 1976 and has become a rage lately, especially among book lovers. Believed to be the largest fair, not just in town but also in all of Asia, the fair is mostly held for the general public instead of the distributors and retailers. With a total footfall of around 2 million visitors, the book fair also has candy floss vendors, pinickers, singers, songwriters and tid bit sellers etc., present in the event. The fair is held on a large scale and has become synonymous with the culture of Kolkata. It won’t be surprising to find people who visit the fair everyday till it\’s duration.</string>
    <string name="kolkata_international_cinema_festival">Kolkata International Cinema Festival is a week long cultural film festival organised in Kolkata. The festival showcases a range of Indian and International films, and is considered to be one of the most loved and most awaited festivals in town, especially by cinema lovers. Organized by West Bengal Film Centre under the West Bengal Government, the festival was founded in 1995 and has been growing ever since. It is one of the most grand affairs in town and is the second oldest international film festival in India. Besides, it features a fine range of documentaries, short films, art films and regional films as well as contemporary films.</string>
    <string name="national_theatre_festival">National Theatre Festival, also known as Nandikar\’s National Theatre Festival is an annual theatre festival held in the city of Kolkata inside the Academy of Fine Arts. The festival was started in 1984 by a theatre group called the Nandikar\’s. But now is an important cultural celebration in town. The festival also features and showcases contemporary and avant garde performances from theatre troupes in India and from other countries like the United States, Sweden, Nepal, Switzerland, Pakistan, and Bangladesh etc. In addition to that, you can also attend workshops and exhibitions that are conducted on the venue itself.</string>
    <string name="international_history_heritage_exhibition">International History &amp; Heritage Exhibition is an annual event organized by the museum - Sabarna Sangrahashala located in Saptarshi Bhawan in Kolkata. The four day programme is based on different themes and showcases important relics and resources from history. There is also a section where one neighbouring country (to India) is selected and in depth detail and information is shared about its history, traditions and cultural ties with India. Besides, there are several talk shows, quizzes and cultural programmes going on simultaneously, in which you can participate.</string>

    // Data for BestSecretActivity.java
    <string name="s1">SECRET 1\nKolkata\'s \"Metro Railway\" was the first underground rail in India!</string>
    <string name="s2">SECRET 2\n\"Calcutta Tramways\" is the only tram service in all of India, and the oldest surviving electric tram network of Asia!</string>
    <string name="s3">SECRET 3\nThe city has an extensive bus network (possibly the most exhaustive in the whole of India) and this is (again most posssibly) the cheapest among all metros in India! The conductors call out their destinations to everyone he\'s passing and all you have to do is wave at the bus anywhere and it will stop!</string>
    <string name="s4">SECRET 4\nLong the world\'s only major metropolis where human-pulled rickshaws were still a major form of transport, a complete ban was supposed to be imposed in November 2006 - but with 35,000 union members who are unlikely to disappear overnight it was not implemented.</string>
    <string name="s5">SECRET 5\nIT sector is one of the prime business area of Kolkata.\na) Its the most influntial sector in Kolkata now. Around 1.2 Lakh people are Employed in Sector V, Kolkata.\nb) The infrastructure, the premises .... the whole look and feel is a must see! This kind of large area, dedicated as IT Hub... is not even available in Bombay/ many other cities in India (Obviously exclusding Bangalore!).\nc) You will get the corporate feeling and professional behaviour there, unlike other parts in Kolkata.\nd) A lot of the Major Software companies located in Here, e.g. IBM, TCS, Accenture, CTS, Wipro, PwC (also serves as the India Head Quarters), Capgemini, Ericsson Global Services, HCL Technologies, NIIT Technologies, Mindteck etc.\ne) Kolkata is rapidly turning into a pro-IT town. More and more businesses are coming to Kolkata to set up their offices.</string>
    <string name="s6">SECRET 6\nA walk along Chowringhee Road sets the pace as you set out to unravel the rare beauty of this city.</string>
    <string name="s7">SECRET 7\nBelieve me or not; Sunset view from Princep ghat can be comparable to Marine Drive view in Bombay!</string>
    <string name="s8">SECRET 8\nKolkata Race Course, built in 1819, is one of the best in the east and is the scene of much gaiety, especially during the winter season.</string>
    <string name="s9">SECRET 9\nKolkata Birla Planetarium is the largest planetarium in Asia and the second largest planetarium in the world!</string>
    <string name="s10">SECRET 10\nDalhousie Square was the administrative centre for British India. On one side is the General Post Office, a majestic specimen of Edwardian architecture. It is built on the site of the original Fort William. On the other side stands Writer\'s Building , a massive Gothic structure with lonic pillars – still the house of political power.</string>
    <string name="s11">SECRET 11\nTagore House, at Jorasanko, is the birth place of Rabindranath Tagore, India’s greatest modern poet. Converted to Rabindra Bharati University, it is now a centre for Indian Classical Fine Arts.</string>
    <string name="s12">SECRET 12\nBelvedere House is now the National Library. It houses over a million books and is the biggest in India!</string>
    <string name="s13">SECRET 13\nKolkata Zoological Garden : Covers 16 hectares of land and built in 1876. The lakes within are a favourite retreat for migratory Siberian birds.</string>
    <string name="s14">SECRET 14\nKalighat : According to the legend, when Lord Shiva\’s wife Parvati\’s body was cut up, one of her fingers fell here. Rebuilt in 1809, this is an important shrine of Hindu Shakti worship. The temple is in the southern part of the city.</string>
    <string name="s15">SECRET 15\nDakshineswar Kali Temple and Belur Math : Built in 1847, on the banks of the Hooghly, north of Calcutta, the temple is associated with Shri Ramakrishna , the eclectic 19th century saint who revived Hinduism during the British Raj. Across the river stands Belur Math, headquarters of Ramakrishna Mission.</string>
    <string name="s16">SECRET 16\nSt John\’s Church : Built in 1787 with Grecian columns. The burial ground has the mausoleum of Job Charnock, founder of Calcutta. On the north-west side of Raj Bhavan.</string>
    <string name="s17">SECRET 17\nSt Paul\’s Cathedral : Constructed between 1839 and 1847 in Gothic style with stained glass windows and two Florentine frescoes, the cathedral is the largest in the city and next to the Birla Planetarium.</string>
    <string name="s18">SECRET 18\nThe Kolkata Book Fair is the largest book fair in Asia (takes place from the last week of January to the first week of February)!</string>
    <string name="s19">SECRET 19\nUniversity of Calcutta Established in 1857 it was the first modern university on the sub-continent.</string>
    <string name="s20">SECRET 20\nBengal Engineering and Science University, Shibpur - Established in 1856. First institute to conduct degree examinations in engineering in Asia(1864). First institute to introduce post-graduate(1954) and also doctoral(1962) programmes in engineering in India.</string>
    <string name="s21">SECRET 21\nFive Nobel Prize winners have been associated with Kolkata:\na) Sir Ronald Ross (1902, Medicine)\nb) Rabindranath Tagore (1913, Literature; first Asian to win the Nobel Prize)\nc) C V Raman (1930, Physics)\nd) Mother Teresa (1979, Peace)\ne) Amartya Sen (1998, Economics)</string>
    <string name="s22">SECRET 22\nOscar Winner: Satyajit Ray.</string>

</resources>